CATALINA GUERRERO

System Engineer

ABOUT ME

I am a resolutive pofessional, proactiv, positive and self-driven, capable of working in an heterogeneous group with a great environment adaptation.

Throughout my academic training I have worked with a variety of technologies for Web Development.

CONTACT DETAILS

WhatsApp:

+54 9 221 542-1221

Email:

catalinango@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/catalinango

GitLab:

https://gitlab.com/catalinango

REFERENCES

LIC. MICAELA GARCÍA MUÑOZ Email: mica.garciam@gmail.com Movil: +54 9 221 602 - 0630

ING. DIEGO SPINEDI

Email: diegospinedi@gmail.com Movil: + 54 9 221 418 - 0286

PROFESSIONAL CAREER

Full Sack Web Developer

Web Site & CMS | Jan 2021 - Present

Backend development for: www.aceroproducciones.com.ar, Content Management System and maintenance.

I have developed a Dashboard Api Rest for CMS including CSS and JavaScript libraries for image management, table sorting and card sorting with drag and drop. For the backend I have implemented Slim PHP & MariaDB.

Technical Support

Government of Bs. As. Province | Mar 2016 - Present IT Support Levels 1, 2 and 3 (full description details in Linkedin). I have gained soft skills that allowed me to work as a team with my co-workers in order to solve their technical issues. I have also learned how to deal with unexpected events and find solutions to complex matters.

Teacher

Technical Training Institute | May 2016 - Present Given Subject: Fundamentals of Web Design (2 H/W) Program: Systems Analisis (3 years Diploma)

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Catholic University of La Plata

Information System Engineer

- Graduated: 2021 (5 years Bachelor Degree)
- GPA: 86,7%

Higher Technical Training Institute N°12

Analyst programmer in application development

- Graduated: 2015 (3 years Diploma)
- GPA: 81,7%

LANGUAGES

- Spanish: Native
- English: Advanced. IELTS Certification: 6.5 (B2)
- German: Basic

SKILLS

- Scrum
- ANGULAR
- GIT
- WordPress
- PHP & MYSQL/MARÍA DB
- JavaScript
- HTML & CSS (Bootstrap)